the right patient group, and so we'll ultimately have to see.
I think some of the other dynamics that will be important is cardiovascular versus stroke
and how those different elements contribute to the primary outcome.
We do have a MACE IV endpoint here, so we do include stroke.
And I think some of the recent literature would suggest stroke is going to be an important
element of the story for Lp level A, so we'll see how that unfolds.
So exciting, but we'll also have to see.
I do want to highlight as well that, as I've already said, we're going to be
looking at some of the other studies that have been articulated in the past.
This will be a slow-building market simply because we need the testing rates to get much
higher.
So this will be, assuming it all plays out as we hope, multiple iterations.
But our DII-235 is ready to go into phase III studies, which could be a once-yearly
Lp level A injection, so we're quite excited about that as well to be ready.
Lastly, I would note that ACC and AHA have now added that everybody in the United States
should receive one dose of Lp level A.
And that's a milestone to hopefully get testing rates up and to start to build the market
over time.
So thanks for the question.
Thanks so much.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Matthew Weston from UBS.
Please go ahead.
Thank you.
My question is about Rapsido.
Vas, now that we're heading to EU approval, Rapsido is going to be one of the first pricing
discussions for a multibillion dollar company.
So assuming that you've had some early discussions with European governments, are you seeing
countries inclined to pay higher prices for innovation in Europe?
Yeah, thanks, Matthew.
So first, it's important to note Rapsido only has an MFN impact for Medicaid because
the approval happened before the signing of our MFN agreements.
Our first launch that we'll have, I think, clear MFN.
Related implications across all segments in the U.S. would be Unalamab.
So I think that's just one clarification.
Nonetheless, I'll still answer the question in terms of the ongoing discussions with governments.
We are engaging with governments across Europe as well as in Japan to hopefully get to a
better place.
I think we're not seeing the progress that we had hoped to see at the pace that we had
hoped to see.
So I think there has to be some urgency here because I do expect across the industry there
will be difficult decisions.